

1206 Huynh Tan Phat St., Obistrict 7, Ho Chi Minh City

About Me

I am a programmer with over 2 year of experience in web programming, and associated web services. Looking to leverage my expertise and professional experience in my upcoming job and further develop my skills and knowledge to advance to higher positions

Skills and Service

- HTML/CSS/JavaScript, ReactJS
- NodeJS, Express , MongoDB
- Git, VSCode, Sentry, Clickup
- AWS Amplify, AWS S3, AWS EC2, Cloudflare, MessageBird
- Image processing with canvas

Education

2018 -2022

4 years

Student | Posts and Telecommunications Institute of Technology

Attending a regular university in information technology majoring in software technology with a training period of 4 and a half years

Work Experience

2020-2021 Intern programmer | Scale Mind Co

6 months I participated in a project to build a website teaching about AI and

machines as a front-end developer, contributing ideas and responsible for user interfaces such as component coding, animations, and ReactJs

interfaces. Slide the PSD into an HTML page.

2022-2023 Front-end developer | Wonder Human Resource &

2 years Axpara

Website programming according to the plan of the company and customers.

User interface design, working with back-end developers and designers

Maintain and develop more features of the website Contribute ideas and design and technology for projects

Learn more about organization, project management and professional

workflow

More information

- github.com/TrongNhan30520
- linkedin.com/in/nhantrong30520
- trongnhan-portfolio.netlify.app

Project

Code claritas.app

website for quality control of high-rise buildings by processing cross-sectional images of buildings taken by drones. Users can annotate images, update repairs, manage buildings and export aggregate reports.

Front-end uses: reactJs, tailwind css, redux thunk and libraries that handle annotations on images (react-image-annotate) as well as export reports in world, excel, pdf formats Hosting services AWS amplify, AWS S3.

My main tasks in the project are: working with an image annotation library - custome the library to suit the requirements, processing images and annotations with canvas, processing world reports, excel, pdf

Code tagrise.com

website connecting jobs between KOL and parties wishing to cooperate. The client side can post articles about the cooperation request and the KOL side can take the work to do. The website allows creating e-wallets and linking banks to make payment transactions Front-end uses: reactJs, tailwind css, redux and services like: Wallex, Directus, Jumio, Stripe, Rudderstack, Clevertap. I am responsible for handling the communication between the two client roles of the website and connecting services to the website.

Realtime Chat Application | Personal project

This is a Chat app with Direct and Group Chats, emojis & Reactions, Built-in Gif support, the ability to edit & delete messages, specialized commands, fully responsive, and much more. I're going to use ReactJS on the front end, NodeJS on the back end and the entire chat is powered with Getstram.io

- Link code: https://github.com/TrongNhan30520/realtime__chat
- Link demo: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=azaqAUB0sHI

Ecommerce Website | End of course project

Position: Frontend Dev, Backend Dev

Teamsize: 3

Project desctiption: This is a final project of the subject "web programming". Our mission is

clone a sales website. And we finished this project in 2 months. Web Technologies: Front-end (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap). Back-end

(Spring MVC, JSP Serverlet, MS SQL Server)

- Link: https://github.com/TrongNhan30520/WebBanDoChoi

- Linh demo: https://youtu.be/NWFURSV1kpc

Story list application| Personal project

- -This is a Full Stack MERN Application with React, Node.js, Express & MongoDB. The app is a simple social media app that allows users to post interesting events that happened in their lives
- Link code: https://github.com/TrongNhan30520/story__list
- Link demo: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I5h2m-IPbG0